<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business 3.0</title>
    <link>https://shenchingtou.github.io/asian-founders-archive/docs/asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Business 3.0</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shenchingtou.github.io/asian-founders-archive/docs/asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Root Impact in Seoul</title>
      <link>https://shenchingtou.github.io/asian-founders-archive/docs/asia/hkelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shenchingtou.github.io/asian-founders-archive/docs/asia/hkelly/</guid>
      <description>Redesigning co-working for impact Archive Date: May 16, 2019
Two years after Root Impact began working to support Changemakers, a pattern of barriers had emerged. By 2014, they began collaboratively designing a co-working space with its potential tenants, and launched HEYGROUND in 2017 with over 90% occupancy. The 6000-square metre space has attracted the attention of mainstream media, companies like Patagonia, and South Korea’s sitting President Moon Jae-in. In 2018, we sat down with HKelly Shin from Root Impact to talk about HEYGROUND’s development and ongoing evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Impact Myanmar (SIM)</title>
      <link>https://shenchingtou.github.io/asian-founders-archive/docs/asia/haraldfriedl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shenchingtou.github.io/asian-founders-archive/docs/asia/haraldfriedl/</guid>
      <description>Preparation in Anticipation for New Markets: Harald Friedl with Social Impact Myanmar (SIM) Archive Date: January 10, 2018
Social Impact Mynamar and MVP development approaches to startup hubs, incubators, and ecosystem support in Yangon while waiting for market maturation.
It was an unassuming white block for a meeting. It was behind a wall, up a teeny slope, and had a restaurant with a patio beside. When Harald came in, still caught in a phone meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>