<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About Business 3.0 on Business 3.0</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About Business 3.0 on Business 3.0</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GoodNotes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/goodnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/goodnotes/</guid>
      <description>Interview with Steven Chan, Founder of GoodNotes: How He Turned an App Idea into a Profitable Business Archive date: May 2, 2019
In his last semester of university, Steven Chan registered for as many bird courses as possible and staked all his efforts into a new app. Since then, he has built his product GoodNotes into an award-winning app featured on Apple’s App Store multiple times. Rather than pursue a venture-backed business model, Steven’s devotion to product development and revenue-driven growth also afforded him the time to pursue other meaningful experiences in life, such as travel and be a digital nomad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day at Impact HUB Tokyo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/day-at-impact-hub-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/day-at-impact-hub-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>A Day at Impact HUB Tokyo Archive date: February 22, 2018
Impact HUB Tokyo hosts a variety of events every week. Why do we bother doing so many though? It’s because these events have a huge impact on ordinary businesses and are the wellsprings for new ideas and collaborations. Every event organized by Impact HUB Tokyo has a clear purpose and goal. We’ll introduce some of them below.
Fostering a culture of learning through failure with Fuckup Nights” Image courtesy of Impact HUB Tokyo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppCoda</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/appcoda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/appcoda/</guid>
      <description>Creating one of the world’s leading iOS tutorial platforms out of a side blog — AppCoda Archive Date: April 19, 2018
Every week, we feature one entrepreneur or startup in East Asia that we respect. This week, we interviewed Simon Ng, Founder and Chief Editor of AppCoda, a leading iOS development tutorial platform.* In our interview with Simon, we covered his entire journey with AppCoda for the past 5 years, which we’ll be separating in to 2 parts: Product and Business Development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BestBev</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/bestbev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/bestbev/</guid>
      <description>How to do guerilla business development for a new industry — BestBev Archive Date: April 19, 2018
BestBev was born in March 2013, and within months had their first shipment of craft beer into Hong Kong. Since then, its Shaheen Budhrani, Shakib Pasha, and Arnold Lee have introduced a host of award-winning overseas beers and ciders into the Hong Kong market and acquired an industry competitor by the end of 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EONIQ</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/eoniq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/eoniq/</guid>
      <description>Creating revenue-generated growth for EONIQ through need finding Archive Date: May 3, 2018
Founded in the summer of 2014, EONIQ is a custom watch brand founded in Hong Kong and that was the first to create customized mechanical watches that are designed by users on its website. Since its founding, EONIQ has always been profit run (with no capital injection), and the company has been featured on Elle, Tech in Asia, and The Next Web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helper Go</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/helpergo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/helpergo/</guid>
      <description>Building a revenue-driven product in 2 years — Sam Ng on HelperGo Part 1 Archive Date: October 8, 2018
Brief: In 2015, Sam Ng was onto his third company after two failed startups in two years. Fast forward to 2018 and Sam’s third company, HelperGo had investment from 500 Startups and reached profitability. Sam’s fourth company was already raising Series A and he had exited to work on his fifth startup, which had already secured investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LaunchPilots</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/launchpilots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/launchpilots/</guid>
      <description>Launchpilots’ multiple iterations until proof of concept to land investment Archive Date: April 22, 2018
In 2011, Jah Ying Chung had organized 300 activities across 20 provinces in China for an NGO, and also helped university student groups get sponsorships from brands like Nike. Getting sponsorships was a common painpoint for all student group and Jah Ying realized there was a market need. She first addressed this need by setting up an NGO that ran workshops to support student organisers and eventually pivoted to an online marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MakerBay</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/makerbay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/makerbay/</guid>
      <description>On finding your first customers in high stakes business: Cesar Harada on setting up MakerBay Archive Date: April 22, 2018
Officially registered in January 2015, MakerBay as Hong Kong’s first co-making space finished renovations and opened its doors to members by Spring the same year. Founded by innovator, environmental activist, and entrepreneur Cesar Harada, MakerBay has since evolved to become a community hub and incubator for makers, startups, and innovators. By 2018, MakerBay had expanded to Central’s PMQ, moved HQs to a multi-storey Tsuen Wan building, collaborated with the Hong Kong Jockey Club to open 6 young makerspaces, and designed maker workstations for schools throughout the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ooosh for Startups</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/ooosh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/ooosh/</guid>
      <description>由荔枝角到觀塘再戰私募基金 Ooosh for startups：客戶成功才是王道！ By : Ten Tang Archive Date: July 4, 2018
客戶成功(Customer Success)不是軟件即服務(SaaS)的專屬名詞！一間在香港的共享工作室，亦憑著「客戶成功才是王道」的經營哲學，不但在短短兩年間擴展到觀塘，更加踩過界大搞私募基金和新創孵化器，致力培養本土的新創公司。這些都是Jeffrey和他的團隊努力的成果。
不怕蝕底，才能與顧客建立長遠的關係 Ooosh for startup 在2016年成立，是一間紮根在荔枝角的共享工作室。短短兩年，Ooosh就吸引了超過50個初創團隊在這10,000尺的空間裡工作。Jeffrey是Ooosh的創辦人，他坦言剛開始的時候，自己在這個行業沒有資源也沒有人脈， 能夠吸引初創公司在Ooosh, 他靠的是四個字 — 不怕蝕底。
「剛開始的時候我們也不太清楚如何能夠幫助初創團隊，所以我常常強調，我們能做到的就是不要計較，我們的職責就是讓他們能夠在這個地方舒舒服服地工作。Be a giver。例如說有人要用會議室但沒有預約，我們會照讓他用，大家溝通好下次用前先預約就好了。」Jeffrey的giver哲學就為他贏了租客的心 — 不但有好幾個團隊打從Ooosh初開張的時候就一直在此工作至今，租客們都非常樂意向朋友介紹Ooosh 。
顧客的成功就是我的成功 Jeffrey在經營Ooosh的時候，大部份的心思都花在如何讓租客可以「有嘢攞走」。而社群管理就是重要的一環。Jeffrey打從一開始就意識到社群的重要性，因為唯有當志同道合的人聚在一起的時候，才能帶起互相學習、互相支持的氛圍。所以Ooosh的團隊在找租客時，很有策略地對準科技新創：一來新創團隊的思想一般比較開明，二來新創團隊的工作很相類似，較容易有共同的話題。
「我最開心的，不是簽了有多大的單，而是租客可以在Ooosh學習到新的知識、有新的啓發可以應用在業務上。」以Ooosh 開業以來最成功的例子，莫過於有位做產品採購的租客，在與其他租客交流時學到了不少軟件開發的知識，因而聘請了程式人員開發了一個簡化作業流程的軟件，拓展業務。
不要只往金錢看，顧客的素質也很重要 Jeffrey很清楚共享工作間的價值，並不在於它所提供的空間，而是這裡的人脈資源。「講真，香港雖然有土地問題，但公司仍有很多選擇：他大可以租一個在工廈的小單位，又或者租一些大型的服務式辦公室。他們為何要選擇你小小的一間共享工作室呢？要吸引他們來，就要能夠提供額外的價值。」因此當Ooosh的團隊招攬租客時，金錢不是唯一的指標；他們希望在Ooosh的租客都是能夠接受新思新的人，這樣才能夠建立一個健康和長遠的社群。
「通常我們對那些很踴躍地問問題、對周遭的環境抱有好奇心的準租客會特別落力推銷；而性格比較惡劣的，沒有辦法，我們通常都不會招呼他們。」Jeffrey對的顧客素質堅持是有回報的。現時Ooosh的會員不但相處融洽、時有交流，每當有新會員加入的時候，他們更會主動地歡迎新成員，甚至比Jeffrey更加熱情！
知多一點 客戶成功一詞的來由：因為軟件即服務的收費模式多為月費訂閱(Monthly Subscription)，所以客戶的忠誠度對他們的收入有很大的影響。而他們發現要提高客戶的忠誠度，只談容戶服務是不足夠的，讓客戶用了你的產品後變得成功才是關鍵！</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 1: Monetisation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/magic-sketch/part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/magic-sketch/part-1/</guid>
      <description>How this solopreneur monetized the right product after multiple wrong successes Archive Date: February 22, 2018
Part 1 of an interview with UX/UI designer and solopreneur, James Tang, creator of the Sketch plug-in Magic Mirror (now Magic Sketch). This interview was conducted in Cantonese, with the English version is a translation with approval from James. Part 1 covers James’ journey in experimenting with ways to generate income after leaving a paid job in Hong Kong’s startup scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 1: Starting</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/asia/helping-hands-yangon/part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/asia/helping-hands-yangon/part-1/</guid>
      <description>How this woman unwittingly became a female founder: Helping Hands Yangon Archive Date: January 18, 2018
How dogged persistence in prototyping for a personal project grew into minimum viable product (MVP) and became a social enterprise called Helping Hands Yangon. Learn how Annie founded this self-sustaining business after realizing there was demand in Myanmar for teak furniture and local Burmese handicrafts.
The women looked from their sewing machines to see who had walked through the 10-foot wooden doors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 2: Pivot</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/magic-sketch/part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/hong-kong/magic-sketch/part-2/</guid>
      <description>How to stay agile and pivot as a solopreneur: James Tang and Magic Sketch Archive Date: February 25, 2018
Part 2 of an interview with UX/UI designer, James Tang, creator of the Sketch plug-ins Magic Sketch and Magic Presenter). This interview was conducted in Cantonese and translated into English. In Part 1, we covered James’ experiments, learnings, and failures before he arrived at his first hit product, Magic Mirror. In Part 2, James shares how he started working on his product and his early mistakes that taught him how to create revenue in hopes that other fellow developers, UX designers, and entrepreneurs can successfully build their ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 2: Recruiting Talent</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/asia/helping-hands-yangon/part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/asia/helping-hands-yangon/part-2/</guid>
      <description>How this female founder used trust as a currency when cash isn’t enough in a Myanmar startup Archive Date: February 21, 2018
This is Part 2 of an interview with Annie, co-founder of the Myanmar startup and social enterprise Pomelo for Myanmar. She shares how she crossed cultural divides to work with and hire local Burmese artisans, street youth, and single mothers. In Part 1, Annie shared how she developed her product for her first social enterprise, Helping Hands Yangon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Root Impact in Seoul</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/asia/hkelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/asia/hkelly/</guid>
      <description>Redesigning co-working for impact Archive Date: May 16, 2019
Two years after Root Impact began working to support Changemakers, a pattern of barriers had emerged. By 2014, they began collaboratively designing a co-working space with its potential tenants, and launched HEYGROUND in 2017 with over 90% occupancy. The 6000-square metre space has attracted the attention of mainstream media, companies like Patagonia, and South Korea’s sitting President Moon Jae-in. In 2018, we sat down with HKelly Shin from Root Impact to talk about HEYGROUND’s development and ongoing evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Impact Myanmar (SIM)</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/asia/haraldfriedl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/asia/haraldfriedl/</guid>
      <description>Preparation in Anticipation for New Markets: Harald Friedl with Social Impact Myanmar (SIM) Archive Date: January 10, 2018
Social Impact Mynamar and MVP development approaches to startup hubs, incubators, and ecosystem support in Yangon while waiting for market maturation.
It was an unassuming white block for a meeting. It was behind a wall, up a teeny slope, and had a restaurant with a patio beside. When Harald came in, still caught in a phone meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space as the community’s experiment lab</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/space/</guid>
      <description>Impact HUB Tokyo: Space as the community’s experiment lab Archive date: June 12, 2018
An open, flexible, and multi-functional space “People First, Space Later” has been part of the Impact HUB Tokyo’s guiding philosophy since its inception. Though space comes after, it is nonetheless essential. For this post, we’ll explore how the Impact HUB Tokyo approaches the concept of “Space” below.
If you work your way down the slope from Meguro Station, you’ll find an old printing factory hidden in the residential alleys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The hosting team and members</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/hosting-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/hosting-team/</guid>
      <description>The hosting team and members BY : ATHENA June 19, 2018
A facilitator of a community “Hosting team” Source: Impact Hub Tokyo Impact HUB Tokyo is a co-working place where Impact Makers get together. Various initiatives are created in order to facilitate collaboration between members. In Part 1, we covered how the design of the space, facilities, and furniture can support innovation. However, no matter how amazing the space is or how many strangers are gathered together…that alone isn’t enough for innovation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on entrepreneurship and climbing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/entrepreneurship-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/entrepreneurship-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts on entrepreneurship and climbing Archive date: May 10, 2018
Editorial Note: The original Japanese word “登山” is a general term that means going up a mountain and can refer to hiking, trekking, climbing, and mountaineering. In this piece, the author is usually referring to hiking, but the translation team has made some editorial decisions based on cultural context.
Many moments, I find myself reflecting on the similarities between climbing and entrepreneurship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is an Impact Maker?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/impact-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/impact-maker/</guid>
      <description>What is an Impact Maker? Archive: March 26, 2018
Questioning + Action = Impact Image courtesy of Impact HUB Tokyo
In February 2013, Impact HUB Tokyo had begun renovations a former print factory’s ground floor. After surviving for two years, co-founders Shino and Shingo, painted the words “Questioning + Action = Impact” on the building’s white wall. The words embody the ethos of the company: it is only though questioning the status quo that we can begin to take action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s a basecamp?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/basecamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/tokyo/hub-tokyo/basecamp/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s a basecamp? Archive date: April 2, 2018
The Basecamp for Extreme Climbers Image courtesy of Impact HUB Tokyo
What differentiates the Impact HUB Tokyo other investor and VC-backed co-working spaces and incubators? The founders, Shino and Shingo, describe their role as a basecamp for alpine climbers. The Impact Makers who question the status quo and take action to create the change they want to see in the world are like the climbers who scale the summits to see the glorious panoramas below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>